飞出个未来
失落的冒险
好消息 各位
Good news everyone!
我把行星快递卖给老妈了
I've sold Planet Express to Mom.
另外 你戴着这顶怪里怪气的帽子干嘛
Also, why are you wearing that funky hat?
哦 这个啊 毫无理由
Oh! This? No reason.
嗯 很可疑 十分的可疑
That was odd. Mighty odd.
你脑子短路了吗 教授
Are you off our net, Professor?
你怎么能把公司卖给老妈
How could you sell the company to Mom?
迫不得已啊 我们一直在亏钱
I had to. We've been losing money.
也许我这个每次都动用一大艘飞船
Perhaps my strategy of using a giant spaceship
来运送一个小包裹的策略
deliver one package at a time
并没有我想的那么明智
wasn't as clever as I thought.
还有 你们仨从来都不收钱
Plus, you three never actually charged anyone.
是啊 真抱歉  - 不好意思
Yeah, sorry about that.  - Sorry.
啊 这太令人弯心了
Aww, this bends!
哦 别大惊小怪 又不是世界末日要来了
Oh, fuff. It's not like this is the end of the world as we know it.
世界末日要来了
This is the end of the world as we know it.
你们有没有注意到
Has anyone never noticed that
弗莱打开电视的时机总是这么巧
Fry always seems to turn on the TV at just the right moment?
在收购了行星快递后
With the recent purchase of Planet Express,
邪恶的企业家"老妈"
evil entrepeneur Mom
现在获得了超过50％的地球拥有权
now owns over 50% of the Earth,
这使她成为了地球的至高首领
making her its supreme ruler.
顶着舆论的压力
At the risk of editorializing,
本记者表示 很高兴看到人类这个可悲物种被占领
this reporter applaudes the demise of the pathetic human species.
现在的情况十分严峻
The situation is indeed grim.
现在 我们转接到老妈的现场讲话
We go now to a live statement from Mom.
哦 别担心 亲爱的孩子们
Ooh, don't worry dearies,
我唯一造成的变化就是
The only change I'm making is that
"地球母亲"现在得叫做"地球老妈"了
Mother Earth will now be called Mom Earth.
啊 还挺萌的
Aww, that's cute!
还有 你们现在全都是我的奴隶了
Also, you're all my slaves.
今晚宵禁之前没有来报到的人
And anyone who doesn't report for duty before curfew tonight
将被我的死亡机器人军团消灭
will be blasted by Hoverbot Death Troopers.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
事后看来 也许确实不该把行星快递卖给她
In hindsight, maybe I shouldn't have sold her Planet Express.
肯定是白内障蒙蔽了我
Must be my hind cataracts.
无论如何 地球已经不安全了
Well, the Earth isn't safe anymore.
作为船长 我提议我们赶快逃离这里
As captain, I propose we get the hell out of here.
遵命 老姐
Amen, sister.
全员登船
To the ship.
哦 不 飞船基本上报废了
Oh, no, the ship's all wind up.
谁会做出这种事情
Who could have done such a thing?
这次不是我 我发誓
It wasn't me this time, I swear.
谁干的不要紧 我们必须赶快把船修好
No matter. We need to repair the ship and we need to do it fast.
丽拉  你赶快去捣鼓一下控制台
Leela, you start banging on the control panel.
这就去
I'm on it.
本德 你负责把飞船掰回原样
Bender, you'll have to bend the ship back into shape.
哦 为什么那些掰活儿总是交给我呢
Man, how come I always have to do all the bending around here?
还有弗莱 你…呃…
And, Fry, you... Uh...
你究竟会做些什么
what exactly do you know how to do?
我会用打嗝念字母表
I can burp the alphabet.
A B D
不 等等
No, wait.
我给你一个任务吧 弗莱
I've got a mission for you, Fry.
去找一把锤子
Find a hammer.
好的 长官
Yes, sir.
哦 发生了什么
Oh... what happened?
你被两吨杂物压扁了
You were crushed under two tons of debris.
然后你死了
And you died.
太搞笑了
It was so funny.
看来你得在现场看见才好笑
I guess you had to be there.
我不明白 如果死在那里的是我 那这个我是谁
I don't get it. If that's me dead over there, who am I here?
这个你也是你 多亏了我的最新发明
You're also you, thanks to my latest invention...
动画重绘仪
...the Reanimator.
每当你死亡 它就会自动产生一个你的复制体
Every time you die, it will automatically make an exact duplicate of you...
根据你的 X光 DNA样本
...based on your x- rays, a DNA sample...
和一些从你的网球鞋里刮下来的碎屑
...and some scrapings from the inside of your tennis shoes.
哇哦 你什么时候发明的
Wow, when did you invent it?
大概一周以前
About a week ago.
从那开始我就一直想杀了你来测试一下
And I've been trying to kill you to test it ever since.
哦 教授 这就是我用生命换来的锤子
Oh, professor, here's the hammer I died getting for you.
哟哦 你留着这破玩意吧
Wha...? Oh, you can keep that piece of junk.
很可惜 还有一部分我无法修复
Sadly, though, there was one part I was unable to repair.
千万别是暗物质引擎
Not the Dark Matter Engine.
暗物质引擎
The Dark Matter Engine.
啊 倒霉
Ah, crap.
但我们不是有一个备用引擎吗
But don't we have a backup engine?
曾经有
We did.
但是我们从来没有用过它 它一直在那儿备着
But we never used it, it being backup and all.
所以我把它典当了
So I pawned.
你把它典当了 为什么
You pawned it? Why?
和每个美国人典当东西的原因一样
For the same reason everyone pawns everything in America.
为了买枪
To get a gun.
好了 弗莱 去典当铺把我们的引擎弄回来
Okey-dokey, Fry, go to the pawnshop and get back our engine.
但外面还在宵禁呢
But there's a curfew.
死亡机器人军团正在街头巡逻着
Hoverbot Death Troopers are roaming the street.
是啊
Ah, yes.
那你就只能走下水道了
Then you'll have to take the sewers.
但下水道有变种人啊
But what about the Sewer Mutants?
我不是给了你一把枪吗
I gave you a gun.
你还想要什么 一件花衣服吗
What do you want, a flowered dress?
现在 别再窝在这儿了 快行动起来
Now, stop being a wussy and get going.
我穿着这个套管显胖吗
Does this casing make me look fat?
别再问我这些了
Stop asking me that.
我知道我本应喜欢机器女人 但有时候
I know I'm supposed to like robot women, but sometimes, well...
你喜欢人类女人
You like human women?
不 机器男人
No, robot men.
哦
Oh.
当我有"鸡行器"可以用的时候
Why use my own legs like an idiot
何必要傻兮兮的自己走路呢
when I can use a Chicken walker?
弗莱 你拿到引擎了 干得好
Fry, you have the engine. Great work.
你让所有人都惊讶了
You surprised us all.
而且这次是惊喜不是惊吓
And pleasantly this time.
是的 弗莱很棒
Yeah, Fry's great.
现在 我们开动吧
Now, let's roll.
副驾驶归我
Shotgun.
好了 引擎已就位
There. The engine's in place.
那个给我很多条命的玩意儿也装备好了
And we've got that gizmo that gives me more lives.
准备起飞
Prepare for liftoff.
再见了 蓝色的大笨球
Farewell, big blue ball of idiots.
宇宙 准备好被征服吧
Universe, prepare to be taken over.
我向你推出 "地球飞船"
I give you Spaceship Earth.
好像有一艘飞船正在飞离地球 老妈
A ship appears to be leaving the planet, Mother.
什么 让我看看
What? Show me.
就在雷达显示屏上
It's right here on the radar screen.
混帐 拉里
Damn it, Larry.
雷达已经淘汰了几个世纪了
Radar's been obsolete for centuries.
使用立体影像系统
Use the stereopticon.
我活该 谢谢
I deserved that. Thank you.
行星快递的飞船
The Planet Express ship.
所以 他们想逃跑是吗 没关系
So they're trying to escape, eh? No matter.
我们只需要像抓小猫一样把他们一网打尽
We'll just have to hunt them down like common kittens.
加大能量
More power.
好的 老妈 长官
Aye, aye, Mom, sir.
加大 加大 用力拉 你这个我的儿子
More, more. Pull harder, you son of a me.
我嘞个妖孽的屁股蛋哟
Sweet butt crust on a cracker.
谁会想到这个悲惨的小星球会重成这样
Who'd have thought this miserable little planet would be so heavy?
嗯 沃尔特就能
Uh, Walt would.
你好大的胆子 沃尔特
How dare you, Walt?
嗷
Ow.
欢迎来到萨尔回收站
Welcomes to Sal's salvage.
我可以为你们做什么
What can I do's youse for?
我需要一个宇宙飞船引擎 没什么特别的
I need a spaceship engine. Nothing special.
嗯 只不过 它必须有足够的力量来移动地球
Well, except it has to be powerful enough to move the Earth.
地球 老天爷啊
The Earth? Holy Jesuses.
要这么做 你将需要一个暗物质引擎
For that, you're gonna needs a Dark Matter Engine.
而且得是很大型的才行
And a big ones at that.
报酬不用担心 因为我很快就会占领全宇宙
Money's no object, as I will soon be taking over the universe.
也许你有所耳闻
Perhaps you've heard of it?
嗯 暗物质发动机
Hmm. A Dark Matter Engines.
你必须找到它的发明者
You're gonna have to finds the guy who inventeds it
休伯特·法斯沃斯
Hubert Farnsworth.
行星快递的那只老山羊
That old goat from Planet Express?
但他刚刚逃走了 那个爱妈的 一无是处的老
But he just got away, that mother-loving, no good piece of...
不要担心 我有很多一个主意
Don't worrys. I gots an idea.
我是说 一个很多主意
I mean, an ideas.
好消息 我给重绘仪编写了程序
Good news. I've programmed the Reanimator...
使它对本德也能起作用了
...to work for Bender as well.
所以现在我可以像弗莱一样死而复生了
So now I can die and come back to life like Fry?
这是我这辈子最开心的一天
This is the happiest day of my life.
我把它们困在吸引光束里了
I gots them in the suck beam.
好极了
Lovely.
哦 我的天呐
Oh, my. Oh, my.
哦 天呐 天呐 天呐
Oh, my, oh, my, oh, my.
大家都保持冷静
Everyone just remain calm.
我们要死了 大难临头各自飞吧
We're gonna die. It's every robot for himself.
嗯 那个机器人似乎正在逃跑
Um, that robot appears to be escaping.
没错 逃向注定的死亡
Yes, escaping to certain death.
嗯 我完蛋了
Well, I'm boned.
我回来了 宝贝
I'm back, baby.
本德 你真是一个机械奇迹
Bender, you mechanical marvel,
你在吗
are you there?
嗯 什么
Huh? What?
谁在说话 是上帝吗
Who said that? Is it God?
不是 虽然我是有他这么老了
No, though I'm as old as him.
哦 你好教授 你在我的脑袋里做什么
Oh. Hey, professor, what are you doing inside my head?
我正在使用你的内置广播进行通话 你好
I'm transmitting over your internal radio. Hello.
我们的飞船还困在吸引光束里
Our ship is still trapped in the suck ray.
我们需要你找到光束的发射源 并把它关掉
We need you to find the source of the beam and disable it.
这对本德我有什么好处
What's in it for me, Bender?
呃 这个…不 我们会营救你
Uh, well... No. We'll rescue you and...
并带你离开这个被遗弃的小行星
...take you with us off this God-forsaken asteroid.
没门
No deal.
我这儿有一盒杂志
I've got a box of magazines...
里面有很多女机器人的写真
...with fembot centerfolds.
收到 完毕并出发
Roger that. Over and out.
该死的机器人 你还没有见识到我的绝招
Cursed robot. You haven't seen the last of me.
除非你死了 否则别让我逮到你 虽然你已经死了
Unless you die before I see you again, in which case you have!
干得好 本德
Good work, Bender.
你救我们脱离了老妈邪恶的关节炎触发器
You saved us from Mom's evil arthritic clutches.
是啊 很好 很好 很好
Yeah, good. Good, good, good.
那么现在呢 教授呢
So, what now, professor?
你要发明出什么拯救世界的东西吗
Are you gonna invent something that saves the day?
你通常都是这么做的
That's what you usually do.
唉 我的发明功力还没有那么厉害
Alas, I'm not that skilled an inventor.
但我知道一个人能做到的人
But I know someone who is.
我的导师和前研究生顾问 阿多维
My mentor and former graduate adviser, Adoy.
他住在波加达星球
He lives here on the planet Bogad.
但那在宇宙中最遥远的角落
But that's in the furthest corner of the universe.
而我们剩余的的暗物质燃料
And we don't have enough dark matter fuel...
甚至不够我们驶出太阳系
...to get out of the solar system.
那么看来你得去找一些燃料来了 丽拉
Then I guess you'll have to find some, Leela.
不
No!
你们无路可逃了 鼻涕脑袋
The jig is up, snot heads.
但我们才从你那里逃走
But we just got away from you.
嗯 当初我在小行星上的时候
Hmm. I probably should have disabled their ship or something...
也许应该把他们的船之类的也关掉
...when I was down on that asteroid.
嗯 吃一堑长一智
Well, live and learn.
你想要什么 老妈
What do you want, Mom?
我想要你的暗物质引擎的设计图
I've come for the blueprints to your Dark Matter Engine.
嗯 那你可不走运了
Well, you're out of luck.
唯一的蓝图只存在于我的大脑里
The only blueprints are here in my head.
呃 好吧 那我就要你的头了
Ugh. Fine. Then we'll take that.
最糟糕的部分是幻影痔疮
The worst part is the phantom hemorrhoids.
为我的斩首报仇
Avenge my decapitation.
现在是时候除掉那些残余的
Now to get rid of the rest of those
行星快递的走狗了 以绝后患
Planet Express jerk-bots once and for all.
很好 一切都很顺利
All right. Everything worked out fine.
哦 不 我们正在直接冲向太阳
Oh, no, we're heading straight into the sun.
我们正在冲向太阳
We're heading into the sun?
不算是我最好的着陆 大家还好吗
Not my best landing. Is everyone all right?
是的 我还好
Yeah, I'm okay.
幸运的是 我摔在了某个柔软的东西上
Fortunately, I landed on something soft.
我也很好 告诉我们超重的机器人朋友 不用谢
I'm fine too. No thanks to our chubby robot friend.
至少飞船还能运行
At least the ship is operational.
我们应该能够轻松离开这里
We should be able to get out of here easily.
除非我们耗尽了暗物质燃料
Unless we're out of dark matter fuel.
我们确实耗尽了
Which we are.
欢迎来到太阳城
不欢迎游客
哇 过来看看
Whoa. Check it out.
小心 弗莱 你不应该直视太阳
Be careful, Fry. You're not supposed to look directly at the sun.
问候 你们来自其他星球的外星人
Greeting, you aliens from other planet.
什么 哦 好的 我来搞定
What? Oh, okay, fine. I got you.
嗯 带我们去见你的领导
Uh, take us to your leader.
我是太阳王 Ra-Ra
I am Ra-Ra the Sun King.
一般来说 这意味着我就是领导
but we have little coup d'etat recently.
但最近我们有点小小的政变
是共产主义的无神论者吗
Was it godless communists?
不 是神 强大的 强大的太阳神
No, it was God. Mighty, mighty Sun God.
显然 他最近迷上了他的信徒的肉味
Apparently, him develop taste for flesh of own worshippers.
太阳人民非常害怕
Sun people so afraid,
他们甚至不敢踏出自家的太阳门
they not even set foot on own sun porches.
司空见惯了 总有人害怕这个神那个神的
Big whoop. Everyone's afraid of some god or another.
其实 我们更害怕不死战士的军队
Actually, we more afraid of army of undead warriors...
太阳神用受难者的骨头制造出来的
...Sun God create from bones of victims.
哦 这个还差不多
Oh, those will get you, all right.
也许如果你们能想办法进入密封的寺庙
Perhaps if you find way into sealed temple...
你们就可以击败太阳神 拯救太阳人民
...you can defeat Sun God and save Sun people.
呃 我确实关心你们差劲的人民 和劣质的寺庙
Gee, I really care about your lame people and your crummy temple...
但 这事儿还是算了吧
...but we're gonna have to pass.
你们会得到丰厚的回报
You'd be handsomely rewarded.
算我一个
I'm in.
那么 忠实的朋友 你们有没有暗物质
So, kemosabe, you got any dark matter?
那可是我们的主要出口产品
It our chief export.
那就这么定了
Then you've got yourself a deal.
嗨 你们两个要去哪儿
Hey, where are you two going?
抱歉 丽拉 很乐意帮你拯救太阳 但我太容易烧着
Sorry, Leela, I'd love to help you save the sun, but I burn easily.
而我太容易烧化 但帮我留着我的那份报酬
And I melt easily. But save me my share of the reward.
好大一台烤面包机
That big toaster.
有大事要发生
Something's about to happen.
那感觉深入骨髓
I can feel it in my bones.
说得不错
Good one.
嗯 你不会觉得上帝也会受伤吧
Huh. You wouldn't think a god could be mortally wounded.
被你发现了
You found me out.
我其实并不是一个神
I'm not really a god.
我只是一个普普通通的
I'm just an ordinary
永恒且无所不知的超智能生命体而已
eternal, omniscient, super-intelligent being.
那么你为什么允许那些人被杀害
So why did you allow all those people to be killed?
当然是为了他们的骨头
For their bones, of course.
我用来创建我的骨器人军队
Which I use to create my army of bone-bots.
骨器人
Bone-bots?
你知道 正常人都用全属来造他们的机器人军队
You know, normal people make their robot armies out of metal.
是的 但我的方式更邪恶
Yes, but my way is more evil.
哇 啊
Whoa! Aah!
邪恶的太阳神已经走了
Evil Sun God is gone.
谢谢你 怪异的独眼女人
Thank you, weird, one-eyed woman.
你拯救了我们的行星
You save our planet.
是恒星 实际上
Star, actually.
无论如何 现在 给你们的奖励
Whatever. And now for reward.
能装满整个油箱的暗物质
Full tank worth dark matter.
好哎 宝贝
Oh, yeah, baby.
我们快加满油 然后离开这个糟糕的鬼地方吧
Let's fuel up and ditch this awful sty.
呃 无意冒犯
Uh, no offense.
不介意 但首先 你们一定要来到寺庙和我们庆祝一番
None taken. But first, you must come to temple and celebrate with us.
寺庙  - 是的
The temple? - Yes.
珍贵的寺庙 所有太阳生命的圣地
Cherished temple. Sacred center of all life on sun.
呃 哈哈哈
Uh... Ha-ha-ha.
我们很想留下 但是 呃
We'd love to stay, but, uh...
我们还有…事情
we've got a, uh, thing.
是的 事情
Yeah, that.
赶紧撤
Cheese it.
真是些好人
Them nice people.
啊 我亲爱的教授脑袋
Ah. My dear professor's head,
有了你的大脑和我的邪恶
with your brains and my evil...
我将很快就能称霸宇宙
...I shall soon take over the universe.
你永远不会得逞的 老妈
You'll never get away with it, Mom.
但我已经把地球变成了一艘巨大的战舰
But I've turned the planet Earth into a gigantic warship.
哦 天哪 这样的话 看来你确实很有可能得逞
Ooh, my. In that case, you probably will get away with it.
哟
Yeow!
好热 哦 天呐 我的头 哦 哦
It's hot! Oh, God, my head! Ooh... ooh!
疼 疼
Pain, pain!
宇宙的角落
这里就是波加达
So this is Bogad?
喔 很阴森 是吧
Whoa, Creepy, huh?
是的 还很丑
Yeah, and ugly.
我无法想象在这里我们会发现什么
I can't imagine what kind of disgusting,
令人恶心的污秽的生物
foul creatures we'll find here.
你们好
Hello.
佐伊博格医生 你在这里做什么
Dr. Zoidberg? What are you doing here?
制做浮雕
Making a cameo.
很高兴见到你们 我的朋友们 和那个机器人
It's so nice to see you, my friends and the robot.
这实在是不太可能
This is so unlikely.
嗨 那个鬼东西是什么
Hey, what's that kajigger?
嗯 我不知道
Mm. I'm not sure.
但从它的体形和长长的舌头判断
But judging by its scales and long tongue...
我敢说这是一匹马
...I'd say it's a horse.
叽哩呱啦 哟呵
Giddyup! Yeehaw!
我是一个牛仔
I'm a cowboy, I am.
肯定就是这里了
This must be the place.
什么事
Yes?
嗯 你是阿多维吗
Um, are you Adoy?
阿多维 我已经很久没有听过这个名字了
Adoy? I haven't heard that name in years.
是的 就是我
Yeah, that's me.
呃 好的 我们是教授派来的
Uh okay. We were sent here by the professor.
啊 我记得那位教授
Ah. I remember the professor.
当然了 那时候 我才是那个叫做教授的人
Of course, back then, I was the one called the professor.
等等 我们说的是哪个教授
Wait, who are we talking about?
哦 倒霉
Oh, boy.
休伯特·法斯沃斯教授
Professor Hubert Farnsworth.
没听说过这人
Never heard of him.
那么 我这个亲爱的老信徒需要我做什么呢
So, what can I do for my dear old protege.
他说你也许能够帮助我们
He said you might be able to help us.
长话短说 老妈切下了他的脑袋
Long story short, Mom cut off his head...
现在她正在试图称霸宇宙
...and now she's trying to take over the universe.
哦 好可怕 真可怕 太可怕了
Oh. Terrible, terrible, terrible.
但是现在我们也做不了什么了
But there's nothing we can do about it now.
所以 谢谢你们来看望我
So it's a good thing you came to me.
这个家伙一点用都没有
This guy's not making any sense.
我可以杀了他吗
Can I kill him?
这是我的最新发明 时间隧道仪
This is my latest invention, the Time Tunneler.
有了它 你可以穿越到过去
With it, you can travel back in time and...
在她变得势不可挡之前阻止她
...stop Mom before she became unstoppable.
或者去赌马 保证能赢很多钱
Or bet on horses I know are gonna win.
再见了 衰货们
So long, suckers.
啊 该死 我还在这里
Ah, man, I'm still here.
你需要先给它充电 阿多维
You need to charge it first, Adoy.
发电机在那边
The power generator is over there.
要去到那里 你们必须
You can get to it along
穿过这条充满流沙的危险道路
this dangerous path, laden with quicksand.
我知道 我知道
I know, I know,
那里确实不是一个建造发电机的好地方
it was a terrible place to build the generator.
对不起 行了吧
I'm sorry. Give me a break here.
但这台时光机有一个手柄 它不管用吗
But the time machine has a hand crank. Doesn't that work?
呃 差不多吧 如果你把手柄转到两分钟的地方
Uh, sort of. If you turn the handle for two minutes...
它就会把宇宙送回到两分钟之前
...it'll send the universe two minutes back in time.
也就是说 它会回到我们转动手柄之前 好哟
So it gets us back to when we started turning the handle? Yippee.
不 等等 要拿到发电机 我们可能只需要这样做
No, wait. That might be all we need to get to the generator.
如果我们中有人足够快的话
If one of us is fast enough.
太棒了 又一个危险的任务
Great, another dangerous mission.
这次轮到哪个倒霉蛋
Who's the sucker this time?
佐伊博格医生
Dr. Zoidberg.
好哎 我是英雄
Hooray, I'm the hero.
好哎 我们什么事情都不用做
Hooray, we don't have to do anything!
好吧 佐伊博格 一旦我开始开始转动
Okay, Zoidberg, once I start cranking...
你只有两分钟的时间赶回到我的视线之内
...you've got two minutes to get to where I can see you.
否则 我就当你已经被杀了 并倒转时间
Otherwise, I'll assume you've been killed and rewind time.
被杀了 嗯
Killed, huh?
我不是医生 但我听得出来那会很痛苦
I'm no doctor, but that sounds painful.
哦 是的 相信我
Oh, it is. Trust me.
祝你好运 怪物诱饵
Good luck, monster bait.
佐伊博格化险为夷
Zoidberg makes it to safety...
人们高兴得沸腾了
...and the crowd goes wild!
佐伊博格拉动杠杆
Zoidberg pulls the lever.
时间隧道仪起作用了
The Time Tunneler is working.
好棒优极了 现在我们可以回到过去对付老妈了
Fantabulistic. Now we can go back in time and fight Mom.
并救回教授
And save the professor.
好好好 随便吧
Yeah, whatever.
再见 英雄们
Goodbye, heroes!
我不知道你们是谁 但我永远不会忘记你们的
I'll never forget you, whoever you were!
那么我现在要做什么 伙计们
So, what should I do now, guys?
有人吗 朋友们
Hello? Friends?
喂
Hello?
一周之前
我们要死了
We're gonna die!
有什么大不了的 我们一整天都在死
What's the big deal? We've been dying all day.
我们比平时更加失控
We're even more out of control than usual.
准备好颠簸的着陆
Prepare for crappy landing.
至少现在我们知道我们的飞船是谁毁掉的了
Well, at least now we know who trashed our ship.
哦 不 已经九点了
Oh, no, it's already 9.
如果我们还想阻止老妈买下行星快递的话
If we wanna stop Mom from having bought Planet Express in the first place,
我们最好抓紧时间了
we better hurry.
到船上去
To the ship.
现在 如果我了解时间悖论的话
Now, if I understand time paradoxes,
我们应该开走好的飞船
we're supposed to take the good ship...
把坏的飞船留给原来的我们 对吗
...and leave the bad ship behind for the original us, right?
坏的留下
The bad behind...
再说一遍
Say again?
哦 进去就是了
Oh. Just get in.
一旦你在这里签了名 行星快递就是我的了
As soon as you sign here, Planet Express will be mine.
我做了什么搞笑的事吗
Did I do something funny?
不 对不起
No. I'm sorry.
我应该等你签完字之后再发出邪恶的笑声
I should save my evil laugh till after you've signed.
那好吧
Okay, then.
不要签 教授 我们来自未来
Don't sign it, professor. We came from the future.
这是一个圈套
It's a trick.
啥
Wha...?
一旦老妈得到了行星快递 她就会占领地球
Once Mom gets Planet Express, she's gonna take over the Earth.
然后她会把地球改造成一个巨大的太空船
And then she's gonna turn it into a giant spaceship...
然后称霸宇宙
...and take over the universe.
哎哟喂 那真是太酷了
Man, that was cool.
地球就像这样
Earth is all:
其他行星就像这样
And the other planets are like:
真滑稽
How droll.
我可以跟你们三个说句话吗
Could I talk to you three over here for a moment?
你往左边一点点
A little to your left.
好极了
Wonderful.
毁灭者退出打靶练习模式
Destructor exiting target-practice mode.
毁灭者启动"杀光所有人类"模式
Destructor initiating kill-all-humans mode.
我至死也一直坚持做我自己
And so I die the way I lived:
作为一个巨型机器人
As a giant robot.
好啊
Yeah.
打得好 弗莱
Nice shooting, Fry.
就这么浪费了一个邪恶机器人
Way to waste that evil robot.
哦 就因为一个机器人想要杀人 他就一定是邪恶的吗
Oh, so just because a robot wants to kill humans, he must be evil?
你的偏见真重 丽拉
That is so prejudiced, Leela.
他刚刚也想杀了你 本德
He wanted to kill you too, Bender.
是吗 这个…
Yeah, well...
你闭嘴
You shut up.
哦 不 重绘仪
Oh, no, the Reanimator.
倒霉 从现在起 我们必须小心行事 别随便死了
Bummer. We'll just have to be careful not to die from now on.
你非要乌鸦嘴
You had to say that.
哦 该死 老妈 只有我才能杀死我的船员
Ooh, damn it, Mom. No one kills my crew except for me.
你受死吧
You're going down.
哦 得了吧 你是不会打女人的
Oh, please. You wouldn't hit a lady.
哦 我想你是对的
Oh, I suppose you're right.
但是我可以这样做
Though I would do this.
嘿呀
Hi-yah!
你打伤了我的髋关节
You broke my hip.
我不在乎
I don't care.
你想得到行星快递 从而称霸宇宙是吗
You wanted Planet Express so you could take over the universe, eh?
我想现在你的邪恶计划已经被挫败了
Well, I guess your evil plan is foiled now...
全靠我穿越时空的船员
...thanks to my time-traveling crew.
但是你必须把行星快递卖给我
But you have to sell Planet Express to me.
你的船员说过它已经发生了
Your crew said it happened...
没有人可以改变时间的连续性
...and no one can alter the continuum of time.
噢 是吗 瞧我的
Oh, yeah? Watch me.
交易取消
The deal is off.
哦 好吧
Oh. Well.
如果我附赠这顶帽子给你呢
How about if I throw in this hat?
嗯
Mm...
好消息 各位
Good news, everyone.
我把行星快递卖给老妈了
I've sold Planet Express to Mom.
哦 你看看这些个名字
Oh. Look at all the names.
是的 确实是好多名字啊
Yeah, it's a lot of names...
但是你不也希望自己的贡献受到致谢吗
... but wouldn't you want credit for something you did?